Finding Aid for the Aron Kuppermann Papers 1946-2012
Caltech Archives
- Writings and Publications, Series 5.
  - Reprints, Subseries 2.
    - "Quantum mechanics of the H + H2 reaction", 1970 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - "Electron scattering by H2 with and without vibrational excitation", 1970 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - "Puzzles in the diffusion kinetics of the radiation chemistry of aqueous solutions", 1970 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - "Linear H + H2: exact and approximate reaction probabilities", 1971 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - "Exact tunneling calculations", 1971 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - "Detection and identification of triplet states of H2O by electron impact", 1971 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - "A test of transition state theory against exact quantum mechanical calculations", 1971 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - "Classical and quantum reaction probabilities and thermal rate constants ?", 1971 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - "Exact and approximate quantum mechanical reaction probabilities and rate constants ?", 1972 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - "Angular dependences of electron impact excitation cross sections of O2", 1972 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - "Comparison of boundry-value and initial-value methods for the accurate quantum mechanical solution of the collinear reactive scattering problem", 1972 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - "Angular distribution of electrons from the photoionization of ethylene", 1972 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - "New Gas Lasers Committee Report on: Electronic transition chemically and electrically excited lasers", 1973 (Box 49, Folder 18)
      Copy of original report.
    - "Interaction of low energy electrons with molecules", 1973 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - "Electron impact excitation of H2O", 1973 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - "Large quantum effects in the collinear F+H2 to FH+ H reaction", 1973 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - "String plucking model for vibrational excitation of molecules", 1973 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - "Exact quantum mechanical reaction probabilities and rate constants for the isotopic collinear H+H2 reactions", 1973 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - "Role of direct and resonant compound state processes ?", 1973 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - "Quantum initial conditions in quassi classical trajectory calculations", 1973 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - "Comparison of semi classical, exact quantum, and quasi classical reactive transition probabilities for the collinear H+H2 reaction", 1973 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - "Triplet states in 1,3-butadiene", 1973 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - "A direct test of the vibrationally adiabatic theory of chemical reactions", 1973 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - "Use of central field potentials for describing H2(D2) elastic scattering by other molecules", 1973 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - "Electronic spectroscopy of s-trans 1,3-butadiene by electron impact", 1973 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - "Central field intermolecular potentials from the differential elastic scattering of H2(D2) by other molecules", 1973 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - "Semi classical S matrix theory of reactive and nonreactive atom-molecule collisions", 1973 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - "Comparison of semi classical, quasi classical and exact quantum transition probabilities for the collinear H+H2 exchange reaction", 1973 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - "Violation of microscopic reversibility and the use of reverse quasi classical trajectories for calculating reaction cross sections", 1974 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - "Diffusion kinetics in radiation chemistry: an assessment", 1974 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - "An apparatus for the production of high isotopic purity deuterium", 1974 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - "Coplanar and collinear quantum mechanical reactive scattering ?", 1974 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - "Abstraction fraction in the reaction of deuterium atoms with HBr and HI", 1974 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - "Electronic spectroscopy of the fluoroethylenes by electron impact", 1974 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - "Electron impact spectroscopy of trans-azomethane", 1974 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - "Automatic mass-spectrometric analysis: preliminary report", 1974 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - "Quantum mechanical reactive scattering: an accuarate three dimensional calculation", 1975 (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - "Electronic spectroscopy pf propadiene (allene) by electron impact", 1975 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - "Angular distributions in the electron impact excitation of Xe at 20 eV", 1975 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - "Electronic spectroscopy of trans-azomethane by electron impact", 1975 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - "Exact quantum, quassi classical, and semi classical reaction probabilities for the collinear F+H2 to FH+H reaction", 1975 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - "Exact quantum, quasi classical, and semi classical reaction probabilities for the collinear F+D2 to FD+D reaction", 1975 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - "A useful mapping of triatomic potential energy surfaces", 1975 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - "The scattering of excited by ground state atoms: application to He2", 1975 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - "A semi-numerical approach to the construction and fitting of triatomic potential energy surfaces", 1975 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - "Dynamical resonances in collinear, coplanar, and three dimensional quantum mechanical reactive scattering", 1975 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - "Singlet to triplet transitions in methyl-substituted ethylenes", 1975 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - "Surface functions for three dimentional reactive scattering", 1976 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - "Electron impact investigation of electronic excitation in furan, thiophene and pyrrole", 1976 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - "Electron impact spectroscopy of the fluoreethylenes", 1976 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - "Excited electronic states of ketene", 1976 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - "Progress in the quantum dynamics of reactive molecular collisions", 1976 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - "Triplet states of furan, thiophene and pyrrole", 1976 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - "Quantum mechanical reactive scattering for planar atom plus diatom systems: Part I- Theory", 1976 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - "Quantum mechanical reactive scattering for planar atom plus diatom systems: Part II- Accurate cross sections for H+H2", 1976 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - "Quantum mechanical reactive scattering for three dimensional atom plus diatom systems: Part I- Theory", 1976 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - "Quantum mechanical reactive scattering for three dimensional atom plus diatom systems: Part II- Accurate cross sections for H+H2", 1976 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - "An exact quantum study of vibrational deactivation by reactive and nonreactive collisions in the collinear isotopic H+HF systems", 1976 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - "Large quantum effects in a model electronically nonadiabatic reaction", 1976 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - "Validity of the adiabatic approximation for vibrational energy transfer in collisions between diatomic molecules", 1976 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - "Variable angle photoelectron spectrometer", 1977 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - "The importance of isotope dependent transmission coefficients in calculating low temperature isotope efects", 1977 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - "Classical dynamics of triatomic systems: energized harmonic molecules", 1977 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - "Angular momentum decoupling approximations in the quantum dynamics of reactive systems", 1977 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - "Low energy, variable angle electron impact excitation of 1,3,5-hexatriene", 1977 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - "Excited electronic states of fluorobenzenes by variable angle electron impact spectroscopy"", 1977 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - "Chemi-ionization in K-I collisions: Part I- Integral cross sections", 1978 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - "Chemi-ionization in K-I collisions: Part II- Differential cross sections", 1978 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - "Doublet to quartet transitions in nitric oxide as detected by electron impact spectroscopy", 1978 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - "Electron impact investigation of excited singlet states in 1,3-butadiene", 1978 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - "Doublet to quartet transitions in nitric oxide as detected by low energy, variable angle electron scattering", 1978 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - "Excited electronic states of 1,3,5-cycloheptatriene", 1978 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - "Detection of a second triplet state in thiophosgene by electron impact spectroscopy", 1978 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - "Photoelectron angular distributions of carbon-carbon Pi electrons in ethylene, benzene, and their fluorinated derivatives", 1978 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - "An accurate determination of the He-Ar van der Waals potential", 1978 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - "An empirical anisotropic intermolecular potential for He+CO2", 1978 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - "Electron impact spectroscopy of the alkynes", 1978 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - "Vibronic structure of the second triplet state of 1,3,5-hexatriene", 1978 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - "Electronic spectroscopy of 1,3,5,7-cyclooctatetraene by low enwrgy, variable angle electron impcat", 1978 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - "Electron impact excitation of low lying electronic states in CS2, OCS and SO2", 1978 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - "Scattering of thermal He beams by crossed atomic and molecular beams: Part I- Sensitivity of the elastic differential cross section to the interatomic potential", 1978 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - "Energy dependence of the differential photoelectron cross sections of molecular nitrogen", 1978 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - "Angular distributions in the photoelectron spectra of brenzene and its monohalogenated derivatives", 1978 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - "Angular distributions in the photoelectron spectroscopy of SF6", 1978 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - "Electronic spectroscopy of polyatomic molecules by low energy, variable angle electron impact", 1979 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - "An exact quantum mechanical transition state theory: Part I- An overview", 1979 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - "Angular distributions in the photoelectron spectroscopy of carbon monoxide", 1979 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - "Investigation of low-lying electronic states in nitromethane by electron impact spectroscopy", 1979 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - "Angular distributions in the photoelectron spectroscopy of furan, thiophene and pyrrole"", 1979 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - "Scattering of thermal He beams by crossed atomic and molecular beams: Part II- The He-Ar van der Waal potential", 1979 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - "Scattering of thermal He beams by crossed atomic and molecular beams: Part III- Anisotropic intermolecular potential ?"", 1979 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - "Electronic spectroscopy of UF6 and WF6 by electron impact", 1979 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - "Scattering of thermal He beams by crossed atomic and molecular beams: Part IV- Spherically symmetric intermolecular potential ?"", 1979 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - "Electronic spectroscopy of benzene and the fluorobenzenes by variable angle electron impact", 1979 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - "Electronic spectroscopy of 1,3-cyclopentadiene ?by electron impact", 1979 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - "Excited electronic states of cyclohexene ? by electron impact spectroscopy", 1979 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - "Comment on 'Theory of collisions between an atom and a diatomic molecule in the body fixed coordinate system", 1979 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - "Photoelectron spectroscopy of ethylene ? at variable angle", 1979 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - "Variable angle photoelectron spectroscopy of the fluoroethylenes", 1979 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - "Theoretical aspects of the mechanism of simple chemical reactions", 1979 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - "Vibrational deactivation on chemically reactive potential surfaces", 1980 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - "Variable angle electron impact excitation of nitromethane", 1980 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - "Detection of the 3A2 state of CS2 by multiphoton ionization", 1980 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - "Hyperspherical coordinates in quantum mechanical collinear reactive scattering", 1980 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      Reprint only.
    - "Collinear quantum mechanical probabilities for the I+HI to IH+I reaction using hyperspherical coordinates", 1981 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - "Accurate quantum calculations of reactive systems", 1981 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - "Few body molecular collisions: Theoretical", 1981 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - "Quantum mechanical coupled channel collision induced dissociation calculations with hyperspherical coordinates", 1981 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - "Reactive scattering resonances and their physical interpretation", 1981 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - "Collision lifetime matrix analysis of the first resonance in the collinear F+H2 ?", 1981 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - "Collinear quantum mechanical probabilities and rate constants for the Br+HCI ... reaction using hyperspherical coordinates", 1982 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - "A Physical interpretation of the collinear reactive scattering resonance in the F+HD, H2, and D2 systems", 1982 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - "Scattering of thermal He beams by crossed atomic and molecular beams: Part V- Unisotropi intermolecular potential ?"", 1983 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - "Doublet to quartet and doublet to doublet electronic transitions in NO2 by electron impact", 1983 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - "Test of variational transition state theory against accurate quantal results for a reaction with very large reaction path curvature and a low barrier", 1984 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - "High energy overtone spectroscopy of some deuterated methanes", 1985 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - "Quantum mechanical partitioning of kinetic energy in collision-induced dissociation", 1985 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - "Quantum mechanical study of the reaction Be+FH (?=0,1) to BeF (?')+H", 1985 (Box 56, Folder 10)
      Manuscript and correspondence only.
    - "Towards a state to state transition state theory", 1985 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - "Collinear quassi classical trajectory study of collision induced dissociation on a model potential energy surface", 1986 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - "Hyperspherical coordinate formulation of the elctron hydrogene atom scattering problem", 1986 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - "A Test of the Babamov-Marcus Vibrationally Adiabatic Theory of hydrogene atom transfer reactions", 1986 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - "Three dimensional quantum mechanical reactive scattering using symmetrized hyperspherical coordinates", 1986 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - "Design and operation of stable intense high temperature arc-discharge source of hydrogene atoms and metastable trihydrogen molecules", 1986 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - "An Electron impact spectroscopy investigation of CH3 and some of its pyrolytic precursors", 1987 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - "Total scattering, surface ionization and photoionization of a beam of H3 metastable molecules", 1987 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - "Lifetime analysis of high energy resonances in three dimensional reactive scattering", 1987 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - "The spectroscopy of the group Vib transition metal hexacarbonyls using the electron impact method", 1987 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - "Electron impact spectroscopy of various diketone compounds", 1987 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - "Eletron impact spectroscopy of acetaldehyde", 1987 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - "Quantum mechanical calculation ? on a realistic potential energy surface", 1987 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - "Reply to comment on 'Total scattering, surface ionization and photoionization ?", 1988 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - "Chemical reaction dynamics", 1988 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - "Gaus-Jordan inversion with pivoting on the Caltech Mark II Hypercube", 1988 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - "Observation and analysis of emission spectra of tungsten hydride", 1988 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - "Mass effect quantum mechanical collision induced dissociation in collinear reactive atom diatomic molecule collisions", 1988 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - "Barrier height dependence of dynamics ?", 1988 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - "Quantum mechanical calculations ? on a realistic potential energy surface", 1988 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - "Collision lifetime matrix analysis of the two lowest energy resonances in the collinear H+H2 system", 1988 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - "The use of local hyper spherical surface functions in scattering theory", 1988 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - "Hyper spherical coordinate reactive scatteing using variational surface functions", 1989 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - "Symmetry analysis of accurate H+H2 resonances for low partial waves", 1989 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - "Calculation of bound rovibrational states on the first electronically excited state of the H2 system", 1990 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - "Numerical study of the geometric phase in the H+H2 reaction", 1990 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - "Quantum mechanical reactive scattering using a high performance distributed memory parallel computer", 1990 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - "Excited electronic potential energy surfaces and transition moments for the H3 system", 1990 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - "Theoretical calculation of experimentally observable consequences of the geometric phase on chemical reaction cross sections", 1991 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - "Prediction of the effect of the geometric phase on product rotational state distributions and integral cross sections", 1993 (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - "The geometric phase effect shows up in chemical reactions", 1993 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - "A New look at symmetrized hyperspherical coordinates", 1994 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - "The importance of the geometric phase effect for the H+D2 to HD+D reaction", 1995 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - "The quantitative prediction and lifetime of a pronounced reactive scattering resonance", 1995 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - "Reactive scattering with row orthonormal hyperspherical coordinates: Part I- Transformation properties and hamiltonian for triatomic systems", 1996 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - "Hyperspherical coordinates in reactive scattering theory", 1996 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - "The geometric phase in reaction dynamics", 1996 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - "Reactive scattering with row orthonormal hyperspherical coordinates: Part II- Transformation properties and hamiltonian for tetraatomic systems", 1997 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - "On the geometric effect on tetra atomic reactions ?", 1998 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - "A Very high accuracy potential energy surface for H3", 1999 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - "Chemically accurate ab initio potential energy surfaces ?", 2000 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - "A Quantum and semi classical study of dynamical resonances ?", 2001 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - "Accurate first derivative nonadiabatic coupling for the H3 system", 2001 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - "Asymptotic analysis of state to state tetraatomic reactions using row orthonormal hyperspherical coordinates", 2001 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - "Hyperspherical harmonics for tetraatomic systems", 2001 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - "Sensitivity of the geometric phase effect to resonances, the potential energy surface, the partial wave sum, and the energy", 2001 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - "An optimal adiabatic to adiabatic transformation ?", 2002 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - "Quantum reaction dynamics for multiple electronic states", 2002 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - "Hyperspherical harmonics for triatomic systems", 2003 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - "Quantum reaction dynamics and hyperspherical harmonics", 2003 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - "Hyperspherical harmonics for tetraatomic systems: Part II- The weak interaction region", 2004 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - "Incorporating the geometric phase effect in triatomic and tetraatomic hyperspherical harmonics", 2006 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - "Use of symbolic algebra in the calculation of hyperspherical harmonics", 2006 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - "Numerical generation of hyperspherical harmonics for tetraatomic systems", 2006 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - "Geometric phase effects in H3 predissociation", 2007 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - "Reactive scattering with row orthonormal hyperspherical coordinates: Part III- Hamiltonian and transformation properties for pentaatomic systems", 2009 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - "Influence of the geometric phase and non adiabatic couplings ?", 2009 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - "Nondiabatic effect in the h+H2 exchange reaction ?", 2009 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - "Analytical derivation of row orthonormal hyperspherical harmonics for triatomic systems", 2009 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - "Reactive scattering with row orthonormal hyperspherical coordinates: Part IV- Four dimensional space Wigner rotation function for pentaatomic systems", 2011 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Reprints by others
    - Fausto W. Lima: "Rela?ão entre a constante de viscosidade de souders e o paracoro", 1948 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - J.A. Breves Filho: "Deslocamentos rigidos", 1951 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Walter Borzani: "Fermenta?ão alcoólica contínua de mosto de mela?o", 1952 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Walter Borzani: "Contribu?ão ao estudo da fermenta?ão alcoólica contínua de mosto de mela?o", 1955 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Fausto W. Lima: "Estudo da coprecipita?ão do sitema bismuto-sulfato de chumbo com auxílio dos respectivos radioisótopos", 1955 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - "Selecta chimica: dedicado á memória de Heinrich Rheinboldt", 1957 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Jörn Marz: "Mode selective bimolecular reactions", 1989 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Wulfman Carl: "On the space of Eigenvectors of molecular quantum mechanics", 1994 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - David J. Tanner: "Semiclassical calculation of chemical reaction dynamics via wavepacket correlation functions", 2000 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - "Edward W. Schlag: "Charge conductivity in peptides", 2000 (Box 61, Folder 19)
- Talks and Meetings, Series 6.
  - Talks given in Israel, December 1968- March 1969 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Folder contains mainly correspondence regarding talks that where given by Kuppermann while spending his sabbatical year in Israel. Some of the correspondence is in Hebrew.
  - "Test of transition state theory against exact quantum mechanical calculations," Symposium on Chemical Dynamics, University of Utah, February 18-20, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - "Calculations on H+H2 to H2+H and the foundations of chemical kinetick," University of Florida seminar, February 26, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - "Variable angle photoelectron spectroscopy," American Chemical Society meeting, Los Angeles, California, March 28-April 2, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - "Propagation techniques in reactive scattering calculations," Symposium on the Theory of Chemical Reactions, Rice University, April 23-24, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - "A Computer controlled gas chromatograph mass spectrometer system," Annual Conference on Mass Spectrometry, Atlanta, Georgia, May 2-5, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Caltech Symposium on Transport Theory, May 6, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Brazil visit (NAS-CNPq Chemistry Program), June 10-19, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    Kuppermann participated in the USA-Brazil Science Cooperation Program of the National Academy of Sciences (USA) and the Conselho Nacional de Pesquisas (Brazil) and served as a member of the Barazil-U.S. Chemistry Program Panel.
  - Institute for Defense, Analyses Laser meeting, San Diego, California, July 1, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Gordon Research Conference on Radiation Chemistry, New Hampton, New Hampshire, July 12-16, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    Kuppermann did not attend.
  - "Propagation techniques in reactive scattering calculations," International Conference on the Physics of Electronic and Atomic Collisions, Amsterdam, The Netherlands, July 26-31, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    Kuppermann did not attend; The talk was given by his graduate student, Joel Bowman.
  - Talk to Pasadena School District science teachers, August 23, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - "Angular distribution of electron from the photoionization of ethylene," International Conference on Electron Spectroscopy, Pacific Grove, California, September 7-10, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 13)